[Music]
TV dinner on the bolden plate.
Late night tweets decide the fate.
Billion dollar bill for another wall.
Rules don't matter if you want it. Come
back.
Sign it fast. Going to check who need to
call if you're on deck. King with the
pin. Wave it in. Feels so good to play
pretend.
Pay
executive day.
Oh wow.
Unlimited play.
[Music]
Woke up late. Grabbed a Big Mac.
Spill ketchup all over a diplomatic
pact.
Throws the tantrum
signs away.
[Applause]
Hoping someone tries to make him obey.
Checks and balances sound like a war.
Toss the Constitution onto the floor.
Sign it fast. Don't read the text. We'll
need to compress when you're deck chain
with the pen. Wave it again. Feels so
good to play. Pretend
[Applause]
[Music]
executive day.
Wo wo. Unlimited play.
[Music]
[Applause]